<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title><![CDATA[Christopher Silva]]></title>
    <link href="/blog/categories/book.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-24T05:57:11+00:00</updated>
    <id>/</id>
        <generator uri="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</generator>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magento book coming soon ...]]></title>
            <link href="/blog/2015/08/24/magento-book-coming-soon"/>
            <updated>2015-08-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <id>/blog/2015/08/24/magento-book-coming-soon</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hallo folks, good morning!</p>

<p>I'm very excited today, or not, because I waked up at <strong>06 am</strong> to accomplish my mission to write this post.</p>

<p>This weekend was quite productive in many aspects and after defining my personal challenge about writing daily during 30 days a post, I was talking with a Brazilian friend (<a href="http://tiagosampaio.com">Tiago Sampaio</a>) about the Magento development market in Brazil and we noticed we don't have a good book covering <em>Magento advanced topics</em>.</p>

<p>Okay, I know we have excellent resources in English but if you want to achieve a good part of the community you must have good things written in a local language.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Ps.: Developers who don't know English are normal in many different countries</p>
</blockquote>

<p>This means: <em>this book will be only in Portuguese</em>. Ok, maybe in the future we translate to English, but it depends on other important factor: acceptance.</p>

<p>To write the book we decided to use the incredible <a href="http://gitbook.com">Gitbook</a> platform (AMAZING!) for writing and distribute, this means that we only will have digital format :D</p>

<p>Well, I can't provide many details now because we are finishing the scope, summary, etc. But our plan is to finish till the end of this year and publish in December or beginning of January/2016 
and according our progress I'll posting here the news about the book, than you can follow this process with us!</p>

<p>I hope you are so excited like me ... Have an awesome week !</p>

<p>Tschüss.</p>
]]></content>
        </entry>
    </feed>