<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title><![CDATA[Christopher Silva]]></title>
    <link href="/blog/categories/offtopic.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-23T14:42:52+00:00</updated>
    <id>/</id>
        <generator uri="http://sculpin.io/">Sculpin</generator>
            <entry>
            <title type="html"><![CDATA[A challenge against myself: 30 days / 30 posts]]></title>
            <link href="/blog/2015/08/23/a-challenge-agains-myself-30-days-30-posts"/>
            <updated>2015-08-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <id>/blog/2015/08/23/a-challenge-agains-myself-30-days-30-posts</id>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="houston%2C-we-have-a-problem%21">Houston, we have a problem!</h3>

<p>Have you started something and after few days stopped or you simply feels like you can't do? Not because you don't know but because isn't your habit, we always have some excuse:
<em>- "Oh, I didn't have time";</em>
<em>- "I don't know how to do it";</em>
<em>- "I'm tired today"</em></p>

<p>I've read a lot of articles and books about getting things done, but this doesn't work for me when the goal is write a simple text, article or blog post. Yes, I always had this lack of commitment when it's about my blog and it kills me.</p>

<p>Every time I sit down to write I can't remember the points seems like I'm a novice in everything or a lot of distractions like twitter, IRC, football (<em>#ilovefootball</em>). Oh my God! I didn't have control of my mind and I'm not respecting the moment reserved for this.</p>

<h3 id="...-work-hard%2C-bitch%21">... Work hard, BITCH!</h3>

<p>I have read a lot of articles and other people experience and then I decided to challenge myself to write daily a new post during 30 days. I'm working to create a new and good habit and to incorporate this in my routine, but the journey isn't easy because we are trained to be lazy and our mind always prefers the comfort zone.</p>

<p>After this, my goal is to write three times a week (Wednesday, Saturday and Sunday), but after my adaptation month I'm sure will be "super easy"! :D</p>

<p>Do you know what's the best way to create a new habit? Share with us below and let's discuss and improve ourselves!</p>
]]></content>
        </entry>
    </feed>